RBRL/082/GGA
Richard B. Russell Library for Political Research and Studies
- IV. Speech Files, 1975-2003; 1.0 box; 1 box and 1 electronic file (1 linear foot)
  - Speech File [Index], [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 1)
  - Abortion, [June 1985] (Box IV.1, Folder 2)
  - Aged, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 3)
  - Apples and Oranges, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 4)
  - Black Unemployment, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 5)
  - Blind, [1985] (Box IV.1, Folder 6)
  - Building Dedication, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 7)
  - Children’s Medical Services, [August 11, 1985] (Box IV.1, Folder 8)
  - Christian Citizenship, [June 1986] (Box IV.1, Folder 9)
  - Citizen Participation, [November 1982] (Box IV.1, Folder 10)
  - Construction Industry, [1983] (Box IV.1, Folder 11)
  - DHR Subcommittee, [1985] (Box IV.1, Folder 12)
  - DUI, [1983] (Box IV.1, Folder 13)
  - The Democratic Party, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 14)
  - Eagle Scouts, [1986] (Box IV.1, Folder 15)
  - The Economy (in Recession), [circa 1975] (Box IV.1, Folder 16)
  - Education, [1978-1984] (Box IV.1, Folder 17)
  - Adult Education, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 18)
  - Why Can’t Johnny Read, [1970s] (Box IV.1, Folder 19)
  - CESAs [Cooperative Education Service Agencies], [1979] (Box IV.1, Folder 20)
  - Eulogy, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 21)
  - Farm City Day, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 22)
  - Forging A New Georgia, [1985] (Box IV.1, Folder 23)
  - Fiscal Responsibility, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 24)
  - Forestry, [1984] (Box IV.1, Folder 25)
  - Formula For Excellence, [1986] (Box IV.1, Folder 26)
  - Free Enterprise, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 27)
  - Georgia Equality Project Speech October, 1999 (Box IV.1, Folder 28)
  - Graduation, [1985] (Box IV.1, Folder 29)
  - The Handicapped, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 30)
  - Highways – Fiscal Responsibility, [July 16, 1978] (Box IV.1, Folder 31)
  - Health Care, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 32)
  - How A Bill Becomes A Law, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 33)
  - Hunters, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 34)
  - Industry, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 35)
  - Inflation – Motor Fuel Tax, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 36)
  - 1987 Issues Speech, [November 7, 1986] (Box IV.1, Folder 37)
  - Issues List – Original, 1988 (Box IV.1, Folder 38)
  - Jefferson Davis Profile, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 39)
  - Labor and The Economy, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 40)
  - Law Enforcement, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 41)
  - Legislative Turnover, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 42)
  - Library Dedication, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 43)
  - Local Option Sales Tax, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 44)
  - Medical Doctors, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 45)
  - Medical School Class, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 46)
  - Mental Retardation, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 47)
  - Mobile Homes, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 48)
  - Tom Murphy Heritage, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 49)
  - New Federalism, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 50)
  - Optimist Creed, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 51)
  - [Political Rally, undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 52)
  - [Politics, undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 53)
  - Private Enterprise, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 54)
  - Problems Legislators Face, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 55)
  - Prospects, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 56)
  - Public Libraries, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 57)
  - Retail Sales, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 58)
  - Retired Legislation/Taxation, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 59)
  - Retired Teachers, [September 2003] (Box IV.1, Folder 60)
  - Retirement, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 61)
  - School Food Service Employees, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 62)
  - Social Services Speech, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 63)
  - Soil and Water Conservation, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 64)
  - Spending Controls, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 65)
  - State Trooper Retirement T. Buck, November 1982 (Box IV.1, Folder 66)
  - Taxes and The Single Parent, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 67)
  - Tax Collectors, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 68)
  - Tax-Retired Federal Employees, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 69)
  - Taxation, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 70)
  - Johnny Isakson Floor Speech [Taxation], 1989 (Box IV.1, Folder 71)
  - Times Are Changing, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 72)
  - Two Georgia’s, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 73)
  - U.S. Constitution, [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 74)
  - Various Speeches by other writers [includes speeches by Ray Barnes, Sonny Perdue and Larry Walker, related to the budget and education, 2000-2003] (Box IV.1, Folder 75)
  - Volunteerism [Charlie Watts], [undated] (Box IV.1, Folder 76)
  - Welfare, [circa 1979] (Box IV.1, Folder 77)
  - Women in Business, [1979] (Box IV.1, Folder 78)
  - Women in Politics, 1981, 1984 (Box IV.1, Folder 79)
  - Women in Real Estate, [1979] (Box IV.1, Folder 80)
  - Women – ERA, [circa 1980] (Box IV.1, Folder 81)
  - Women’s Issues, [1984, 1986] (Box IV.1, Folder 82)
  - Women’s Rights, [1981] (Box IV.1, Folder 83)
  - Speech to Retired Teachers, [User Copy, Retiredteachers.pdf], September 2003 (Item EM-362-367)
- V. Research Files, 1974-2004; 3.0 boxes; (3 linear feet)
  Arranged alphabetically, this series contains 115 research files covering topics related to Georgia including education, taxation, and women’s rights. Many of the research files correspond with the speech files.
  - Research File [index], undated (Box V.1, Folder 1)
  - Acid Rain, [May 29, 1984] (Box V.1, Folder 2)
  - Aging, undated (Box V.1, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, [undated] (Box V.1, Folder 4)
  - Alcoholism, [August 1979] (Box V.1, Folder 5)
  - APDC’s [Area Planning and Development Commission], [1977] (Box V.1, Folder 6)
  - [BCCI (Bank of Credit and Commerce International), 1991] (Box V.1, Folder 7)
  - [Bill Shipp’s Georgia and Georgia Beat, 1995-1998] (Box V.1, Folder 8)
  - Block Grants – Social Services, [1982] (Box V.1, Folder 9)
  - Budget Cutting, 1975-1976 (Box V.1, Folder 10)
  - Governor George E. Busbee, [1974-1976] (Box V.1, Folder 11)
  - [Budget, (folder 1 of 2), 2001] (Box V.1, Folder 12)
  - The Governors Amended Budget Report (folder 2 of 2) [Photograph, 1(8x10) color.], 2001 (Box V.1, Folder 13)
  - Carter, Jimmy, [undated] (Box V.1, Folder 14)
  - Child Abuse in Georgia, [1984] (Box V.1, Folder 15)
  - Child Care Credit, [undated] (Box V.1, Folder 16)
  - Child Support Paternity Laws, [undated] (Box V.1, Folder 17)
  - Child Support, [1985] (Box V.1, Folder 18)
  - Common Cause, [1975-1976] (Box V.1, Folder 19)
  - Constitution, New, [1982] (Box V.1, Folder 20)
  - 1976 Constitutional Amendments (Box V.1, Folder 21)
  - Constitutional Revision (Folder 1 of 2), 1981 (Box V.1, Folder 22)
  - Constitutional Revision (Folder 2 of 2) [Photographs, 1 (3x5) color; 5 (5x7) b/w; 35 mm film], 1981 (Box V.1, Folder 23)
  - County Consolidation Hearings, [1985] (Box V.1, Folder 24)
  - Criminal Justice Improvement Council, [January 1985] (Box V.1, Folder 25)
  - Jefferson Davis, [June 3, 1904] (Box V.1, Folder 26)
  - Deaf Education, [November 20, 1985] (Box V.1, Folder 27)
  - Demographics, [undated] (Box V.1, Folder 28)
  - [Department of Corrections, 2003-2004] (Box V.1, Folder 29)
  - Drug Clippings Supplement, [1979] (Box V.1, Folder 30)
  - Drug/Smuggling/Laws, [1979] (Box V.1, Folder 31)
  - Stop Drugs, [1983] (Box V.1, Folder 32)
  - Drug Trafficking – Georgia, [1979] (Box V.1, Folder 33)
  - Economic Development, [1985] (Box V.1, Folder 34)
  - Education, [November 27, 1976] (Box V.1, Folder 35)
  - Elberton Granite Marker, [April 7, 1976] (Box V.1, Folder 36)
  - Elections – 1978, [August 8, 1978 – November 8, 1978] (Box V.1, Folder 37)
  - Emergency Medical Service, [undated] (Box V.1, Folder 38)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, [undated] (Box V.1, Folder 39)
  - False Identification, [April 11, 1984] (Box V.1, Folder 40)
  - Freeport (Folder 1 of 2), [August 11, 1975] (Box V.1, Folder 41)
  - Freeport (Folder 2 of 2), [undated] (Box V.1, Folder 42)
  - Four Year Terms, [January 18, 1977 – May 23, 1977] (Box V.1, Folder 43)
  - GA Institute of Technology, [undated] (Box V.1, Folder 44)
  - Handgun Control, [1975-1976] (Box V.1, Folder 45)
  - Health Maintenance Organizations, [undated] (Box V.1, Folder 46)
  - Heritage Trust Act of 1975, [November 1978-November 1979] (Box V.1, Folder 47)
  - Holidays/State, [October 3, 1985] (Box V.1, Folder 48)
  - Hospital Cost Containment, [April 1985 – August 1985] (Box V.1, Folder 49)
  - [House Insurance Committee, 2004] (Box V.1, Folder 50)
  - Immigration, [2000-2004] (Box V.1, Folder 51)
  - Interim Articles [House Ethics Committee, 1993] (Box V.1, Folder 52)
  - Infant Mortality, November 1985 – March 5, 1986] (Box V.1, Folder 53)
  - Jekyll Island Authority, [undated] (Box V.1, Folder 54)
  - Job Training Partnership, [1983] (Box V.1, Folder 55)
  - Journalism Under Fire, Media/Press Relations, [undated] (Box V.1, Folder 56)
  - Justice Assistance/Block Grants, [1985] (Box V.1, Folder 57)
  - Laetrile, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Branch Budgets, [November 1983] (Box V.2, Folder 2)
  - Local Option Sales Tax, [1975] (Box V.2, Folder 3)
  - Lotteries, [January 19, 1986 – February 26, 1986] (Box V.2, Folder 4)
  - Marijuana, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 5)
  - Mathis, Representative Dawson, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 6)
  - Milestones/20 Years in Georgia Government, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 7)
  - Media – Crisis of Confidence, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 8)
  - Military in Georgia, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 9)
  - Minority, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 10)
  - Motor Vehicle Department Reorganization, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 11)
  - [Thomas B. Murphy, 1975, 1986] (Box V.2, Folder 12)
  - Murphy-Carter Debates, [January 27, 1974 – January 15, 1976] (Box V.2, Folder 13)
  - [Maynard Jackson/Tom Murphy clippings, 1978-1979] (Box V.2, Folder 14)
  - National Conference State Legislature [Folder 1 of 2], [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 15)
  - National Conference State Legislature [Folder 2 of 2], [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 16)
  - Natural Resources, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 17)
  - Newsweek Gallup Poll, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 18)
  - Wiley Nixon, [January 14, 1984] (Box V.2, Folder 19)
  - Nuclear Energy Power Plant, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 20)
  - Senator Sam Nunn, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 21)
  - Pari Mutual Racing, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 22)
  - Party Control – 50 Legislatures, [1984] (Box V.2, Folder 23)
  - Patriotism, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 24)
  - Pensions, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 25)
  - Pension – George Busbee Involuntary Separation, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 26)
  - Perdue, Tom, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 27)
  - Planning and Community Affairs, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 28)
  - Points of Leadership, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 29)
  - Population Growth – Income Distribution, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 30)
  - Post Session Speech 1978, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 31)
  - Pre-Legislative Forum, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 32)
  - Pre-Session Speech, 1979 (Box V.2, Folder 33)
  - Pre-Session Speech 1980, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 34)
  - Press Lists, 1974 – 1975 (Box V.2, Folder 35)
  - Press Passes Session, 1977 (Box V.2, Folder 36)
  - Prisons – Budgets, 1975 – 1983 (Box V.2, Folder 37)
  - Prison System, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 38)
  - Public Television, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 39)
  - PLANES Hobby Planes, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 40)
  - Quality of Life, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 41)
  - Questionnaire, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 42)
  - Reapportionment File - (folder 1 of 2), 1981 (Box V.2, Folder 43)
  - Reapportionment File, (Folder 2of 2) [Photographs, 3 (5x7) b/w.], 1981 (Box V.2, Folder 44)
  - Recall Legislation, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 45)
  - Regional Primary (Presidential) (Folder 1 of 2), [1975, 1986] (Box V.2, Folder 46)
  - Regional Primary (Presidential) (Folder 2 of 2), [1975, 1986] (Box V.2, Folder 47)
  - Religion – Government, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 48)
  - Memo: Ron Carter, Revocation of House Media Credential, [1977] (Box V.2, Folder 49)
  - Rules Ethics, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 50)
  - Salaries and Compensation N.C.S.L. Information, [undated] (Box V.2, Folder 51)
  - Scientific Creation, [October 17, 1983] (Box V.2, Folder 52)
  - Seatbelts, [December 18, 1984] (Box V.2, Folder 53)
  - Session – 1976 – Week In Review, [January 15, 1976 – March 5, 1976] (Box V.2, Folder 54)
  - Session – End of Session Speeches, 1977 (Box V.2, Folder 55)
  - Southern Legislative Conference, [1982] (Box V.2, Folder 56)
  - Speaker [Tom B. Murphy, 1976-1979] (Box V.2, Folder 57)
  - Staggered Tags [Motored Vehicles Registration], 1985 (Box V.2, Folder 58)
  - State Headlines – Council of State Governments [Various publications, “State Government News,” “State Headlines,” State Legislature,”] (Folder 1 of 5), 1975-1978 (Box V.3, Folder 1)
  - State Headlines – Council of State Governments (Folder 2 of 5), [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 2)
  - State Headlines – Council of State Governments (Folder 3 of 5), [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 3)
  - State Headlines – Council of State Governments (Folder 4 of 5), [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 4)
  - State Headlines – Council of State Governments (Folder 5 of 5), [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 5)
  - State Legislature, [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 6)
  - Steel Leghold Trap Legislation, [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 7)
  - Taxation – 1 cent Sales Increase Exemptions, [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 8)
  - Telephone – Measured Service, [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 9)
  - United States Supreme Court, [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 10)
  - Urban Georgia, [August 1979] (Box V.3, Folder 11)
  - Universal Living Wages, [2003] (Box V.3, Folder 12)
  - University Enrollment, [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 13)
  - University of Georgia – Jan Kemp, [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 14)
  - University of Georgia Dean William Tate, [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 15)
  - University System, [undated] (Box V.3, Folder 16)
  - University System, 1985-1986 (Box V.3, Folder 17)
  - [Water Plan Study, 2002] (Box V.3, Folder 18)
  - [Ways and Means Committee, 2004] (Box V.3, Folder 19)
  - Wine Production in Georgia, [1982] (Box V.3, Folder 20)
  - Women in Georgia Legislature, [1983] (Box V.3, Folder 21)
- VI. Presentations, 1985-2003; 3.0 boxes; (3 linear feet)
  The material in this series is arranged chronologically and organized into two sub-series: A. Scripts and B. Slides. The slides depict images of legislators in session and also contain text relating to various types of legislation. Topics include the HOPE Scholarship, education, child protection, and business.
  - A. Scripts, 1985-1994; 11 folders and 1 electronic file
    This sub-series is comprised of eleven folders containing scripts, music and graphics information, and announcements corresponding to the House slideshows.
    - Slide Show, 1987 (Box VI.1, Folder 1)
    - Slide Show, 1988 (Box VI.1, Folder 2)
    - [“Creating Workforce Housing in Midtown/Downtown/Buckhead: A plan for Action,” presentation], undated (Box VI.1, Folder 3)
    - Slide Show, 1994 (Box VI.1, Folder 4)
    - Slide Show, graphics information/music information, 1991 (Box VI.1, Folder 5)
    - Slide Show Script Graphic Slides, 1992 (Box VI.1, Folder 6)
    - Slide Show, 1990 (Box VI.1, Folder 7)
    - Appointments 1986, [March 18, 1985 – October 11, 1985] (Box VI.1, Folder 8)
    - Slide Show Letter, April 6, 1989 (Box VI.1, Folder 9)
    - [1988 House Information Slide Show announcement] (Box VI.1, Folder 10)
    - After Session Memo to House Members, March 21, 1985 (Box VI.1, Folder 11)
    - Slide show for first session of the 147th Georgia General Assembly, [User Copy, slideshow_2003.pdf], circa 2003 (Item EM-362-367)
  - B. Slides, 1991-2003; 5277.0 slides
    5277 slides grouped by presentation and loosely arranged by date, this sub-series includes images of various legislators, presentation graphics, and text slides relating to legislation. Topics include the HOPE Scholarship, education, child protection, and business.
    - [Representatives in session, A-F] (214 slides), 1991 (Box VI.2, Folder 1)
    - [Representatives in session, F-M] (213 slides), 1991 (Box VI.2, Folder 2)
    - [Representatives in session, M-T] (213 slides), 1991 (Box VI.2, Folder 3)
    - [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (212 slides), Miscellaneous [Representatives in session, undated] (196 slides), 1991, undated (Box VI.2, Folder 4)
    - Capital and Surrounding Buildings (196 slides), Business [Various businesses], Speaker and Government [Tom Murphy], 1991 [Representatives in session,miscellaneous] (213 slides), 1992 [Representatives in session,miscellaneous], 1991, 1992 (Box VI.2, Folder 5)
    - 1991 [Representatives in session,miscellaneous] (213 slides), 1992 [Representatives in session,miscellaneous], 1991, 1992 (Box VI.2, Folder 6)
    - Children [Various pictures of children in park] (214 slides), 1992 [Representatives in session,miscellaneous, 1992 Legislative Session Presentation], 1993 [Representatives in session,miscellaneous, 1993 Legislative Session Presentation], 1995 [Representatives in session,miscellaneous, 1995 Legislative Session Presentation], Miscellaneous [Representatives in session, undated], 1992, 1993, 1995, undated (Box VI.2, Folder 7)
    - [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (206 slides), 1993 (Box VI.2, Folder 8)
    - [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (212 slides), 1993 (Box VI.2, Folder 9)
    - 1993 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (213 slides), 1994 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous], 1993-1994 (Box VI.2, Folder 10)
    - 1994 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (214 slides) (Box VI.2, Folder 11)
    - 1994 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (213 slides), 1995 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous], 1994-1995 (Box VI.2, Folder 12)
    - 1995 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (208 slides), 1996 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous], 1995-1996 (Box VI.2, Folder 13)
    - [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (214 slides), 1997 (Box VI.2, Folder 14)
    - [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (176 slides) (Box VI.2, Folder 15)
    - [Representatives in session, miscellaneous, 1997 Legislative Session Presentation] (211 slides), 1998 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous, 1998 Legislative Session Presentation], 1999 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous, 1999 Legislative Session Presentation], 1997-1999 (Box VI.3, Folder 1)
    - 1997 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (213 slides), 1998 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous], 1999 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous], 1997-1999 (Box VI.3, Folder 2)
    - [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (73 slides), 1999 (Box VI.3, Folder 3)
    - 1991 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (212 slides), 1999 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous, 1999 Legislative Session Presentation], 2001 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous, 2001 Legislative Session Presentation], 2002 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous, 2002 Legislative Session Presentation], 2003 [Representatives in session, miscellaneous, 2003 Legislative Session Presentation], 1991, 2001-2003 (Box VI.3, Folder 4)
    - HOPE ["Expanded HOPE Scholarship" Presentation] (197 slides), Child Protection [Various children in a park], Education [Representatives in sssion, miscellaneous, loose presentations], Miscellaneious [Loose Presentations and Governor Sonny Perdue] (Box VI.3, Folder 5)
    - Craig Brock (204 slides), Miscellaneous [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (204 slides) (Box VI.3, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (212 slides) (Box VI.3, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (210 slides) (Box VI.3, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous [Representatives in session, miscellaneous] (214 slides) (Box VI.3, Folder 9)
- VII. Photographs, 1985-2003; 21.0 boxes; (23 linear feet)
  This series consists of photographs and negatives maintained by the House Photographer and are organized into two sub-series: A. Member Photographs and B. Daily Photographs. The member photographs are arranged alphabetically by the member’s name and daily photographs are arranged chronologically. Additional member photographs are located in Series III: Member Files, sub-series B: Photographs.
  - A. Member Photographs, 1999, undated; 1229 photographs, 466 negatives, and 1 electronic file
    This sub-series is arranged alphabetically by member and contains black and white and color official portraits of members of House. Additional member photographs are located in Series III: Member Files, sub-series B: Photographs.
    - Ben Allen, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 1)
    - Amos Anderson, [Portraits, 6 (3.5x5 5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 2)
    - Alberta Anderson, [Portraits, 3 (5x7); 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 3)
    - Kathy Ashe, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5 5x7) color; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 4)
    - Frank Bailey, [Portraits, 2 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 5)
    - Charles Banister, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 6)
    - Fisher Barfoot, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 7)
    - Terry Barnard, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 4 (3.5x5 5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 8)
    - Mike Barnes, [Portraits, 2 (3.5x5) color; 4 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 9)
    - Roy Barnes, [1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 10)
    - Kermit Bates, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 11)
    - Jackie Beavers, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 12)
    - Jimmy Benefield, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 13)
    - Tommy Benton, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 14)
    - Ken Birdsong, [Portraits, 1 (3.5x5) color; 1 (8x10) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 15)
    - Ellis Black, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color; 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box VII.1, Folder 16)
    - Mike Boggs, [Portraits, 6 (3.5x5 5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 17)
    - Pam Bohannon, [Portraits, 9 ( 3x5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box VII.1, Folder 18)
    - Tom Bordeaux, [Portraits, 2 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 6 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 19)
    - Ron Borders, [Portraits, 1 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 20)
    - Frank Bradford, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 21)
    - Keith Bradford, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 22)
    - Ben Bridges, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 23)
    - Craig Brock, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5 color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 24)
    - Tyrone Brooks, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) b/w; 3 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 25)
    - Hugh Broome, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 26)
    - Jeff Brown, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5 5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 27)
    - Roger Bruce, [Portraits, 6 (3.5x5 5x7) color; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 28)
    - Sewell Brumby, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 29)
    - Bob Bryant, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 30)
    - Tom Buck, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 2 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 31)
    - Debbie Buckner, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 32)
    - Gail Buckner, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 33)
    - John Bulloch, [Portraits, 2 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 34)
    - Mark Burkhalter, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 35)
    - Sue Burmeister, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 4 (3.5x5 5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 36)
    - John Burns, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box VII.1, Folder 37)